Personal details

Name: Joey ter Meulen Location: Barcelona, Spain Phone: 0034 679 308 440

E-mail: joeytermeulen@gmail.com

Date of birth: 16-02-1989

Nationality: Dutch

Overview

Hello! I am Joey, a 31-year-old frontend web developer from Amsterdam, the Netherlands. In 2017 I discovered coding and after extensive home studies, I officially joined the development industry at the start of 2018. I have since been professionally developing websites, focusing on React.js, Node.js and GraphQI.

With 3 years of working experience, React.js is my main strength - but in my spare time, Unity and C# take over. Coding games is just as fun!

I recently moved to Barcelona and I'm looking for a fresh new challenge at a company that champions their team spirit as much as their product. I enjoy working with other crafts, collaborating daily with UI/UX, QA and backend developers. I'm always open to feedback and new ideas and can handle stress very well. I am organised, make quick decisions and I can lead a group when I need to.

Job experience

April 2018 -December 2020 **LeoVegas** Luntmakargatan 18, 111 37 Stockholm, Sweden

Occupation: Frontend WebDeveloper (fulltime, 40 hours a week)

Job description: LeoVegas is an online casino provider. My daily job includes developing

new features, especially to enhance the game experience for players. I work with React.js, Node.js and GraphQL on a daily basis. Other responsibilities include writing tests for the features we develop, maintain and bug-fix any feature previously released, and close collaboration between designers and BackEnd developers. In my nearly 3 years at LeoVegas, I have gone from junior to senior within the company. I functioned as interim team-lead for 4 months, where I guided the project from start to finish while coding and

managing team members and stakeholders.

September 2016 -January 2018 Swagg Elektravägen 5, 126 30 Hägersten, Sweden

Occupation: Textile printer (fulltime, 40 hours a week)

July 2015 - Expeditors Ganderweg 1, 1118 LH, Schiphol, Netherlands July 2016

Occupation: Warehouse employee (fulltime, 40 hours a week)

January 2009 - **Refero** Kollenbergweg 78B, 1101 AV, Amsterdam, Netherlands July 2015

Occupation: Textile printer, manager (fulltime, 40 hours a week)

January 2008 - **Schiphol Airport** employment agency Content, Amsterdam, Netherlands January 209

Occupation: Flight Ramp agent (36 hours a week)

Skills

Javascript React.js HTML5 CSS Redux Node.js •••••• **Express** •••••0000 C# / Unity •••••0000 **Python**

Education and Courses

2020	CodeWithMosh - <u>Java Mastery Series</u>
2020	Udemy - Node.JS Advanced Course
2019	Udemy - Unity 2D Game Dev Course
2019	Udemy - <u>Unreal Engine Game Dev Course</u>
2010	Ildamy - FCMAScript 6 Course

2018 Udemy - <u>ECMAScript 6 Course</u> 2018 Udemy - <u>React Complete Guide</u>

2017 **Udemy -** Advanced Web Developer Bootcamp

2017 Udemy - Web Developer Bootcamp

2017 LearnCodeTheHardWay - Book on the principles of coding in Python

2007-2008 InHolland - HBO Commercial Economics
2001-2007 Calandlyceum Amsterdam - HAVO Graduated